<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="castle_paragraph">
        The Royal Palace was built in the first half of the
        19th century as the Norwegian residence of the
        French-born King Charles III of Norway, who reigned
        as king of Norway and Sweden. The palace is the
        official residence of the current Norwegian monarch
        while the Crown Prince resides at Skaugum in Asker west
        of Oslo. The palace is located at the end of Karl Johans
        gate in central Oslo and is surrounded by the Palace Park
        with the Palace Square in the front.</string>

    <string name="opera_paragraph">
        The Oslo Opera House is the home of The Norwegian National
        Opera and Ballet, and the national opera theatre in Norway.
        The building is situated in the Bjørvika neighbourhood of
        central Oslo, at the head of the Oslofjord. The angled
        exterior surfaces of the building are covered with marble
        from Carrara, Italy and white granite and make it appear to
        rise from the water. It is the largest cultural building
        constructed in Norway.
    </string>

    <string name="cityhall_paragraph">
        Oslo City Hall is a municipal building in Oslo, the capital
        of Norway. It houses the city council, the citys
        administration and various other municipal organisations.
        The building as it stands today was constructed between 1931
        and 1950. Oslo City Hall is built of red brick and has two
        towers, one 63 meters tall and other 66 meters tall.
    </string>

    <string name="parlament_paragraph">
        The Parliament is the supreme legislature of Norway, established
        in 1814 by the Constitution of Norway. It is located in Oslo.
        The unicameral parliament has 169 members, and is elected every
        four years. The Parliament of Norway Building opened in 1866.
    </string>

    <string name="skijumping_paragraph">
        Holmenkollbakken is a large ski jumping hill located at
        Holmenkollen in Oslo, Norway. It has a hill size of HS134,
        a construction point of K-120, and a capacity for 70,000 spectators.
        Holmenkollen ski jump hill is the most visited tourist site of
        Norway.
    </string>

    <string name="crosscountry_paragraph">
        Cross country is the national sport. Norwegian army units were
        skiing for sport (and prizes) in the 18th century. Starting in
        the latter part of the 20th century, technique evolved from the
        striding in-track classic technique to include skate-skiing,
        which occurs on courses that have been groomed with wide lanes
        for those using the technique.
    </string>

    <string name="alpine_paragraph">
        The largest ski resort in the Oslo area, with 18 slopes and 11 lifts,
        just 30 minutes from the city centre. Oslo Winter Park includes a
        terrain park in the Hyttli area, cruising slopes in Tryvann, challenging
        slopes and an express lift in Wyller, and slopes for children and beginners.
        The season usually lasts from November/December until the end of Easter.
        Reduced opening hours during Christmas and Easter. Group discounts for
        businesses and school children.
    </string>

    <string name="munch_paragraph">
        Munch Museum is an art museum in Oslo, Norway
        dedicated to the life and works of the Norwegian artist Edvard Munch.
        The museum now has in its permanent collection well over half of the
        artists entire production of paintings and at least one copy of all
        his prints. This amounts to over 1,200 paintings, 18,000 prints,
        six sculptures, as well as 500 plates, 2,240 books, and various other
        items. The museum also contains educational and conservation sections,
        and has facilities for the performing arts.
    </string>

    <string name="fram_paragraph">
        The Fram Museum is a museum telling the story
        of Norwegian polar exploration. It is located on the peninsula of Bygdøy
        in Oslo. The Fram Museum is centered principally on the original
        exploration vessel Fram. The original interior of Fram is intact and
        visitors can go inside the ship to view it. Fram was commissioned,
        designed, and built by Scots-Norwegian shipbuilder Colin Archer to
        specifications provided by Norwegian Arctic explorer Fridtjof Nansen.
    </string>

    <string name="viking_paragraph">
        The Viking Ship Museum is located at Bygdøy in Oslo. The museum is most
        famous for the completely whole Oseberg ship, excavated from the largest
        known ship burial in the world. Other main attractions at the Viking Ship
        Museum are the Gokstad ship and Tune ship. Additionally, the Viking Age
        display includes sledges, beds, a horse cart, wood carving, tent components,
        buckets and other grave goods.
    </string>

    <string name="constitutionday_paragraph">
        A noteworthy aspect of the Norwegian Constitution Day is its very non-military
        nature. All over Norway, childrens parades with an abundance of flags form the
        central elements of the celebration. The longest parade is in Oslo,
        where some 100,000 people travel to the city centre to participate in the main
        festivities. The massive Oslo parade includes some 100 schools, marching bands,
        and passes the royal palace where the royal family greet the people from the main
        balcony.
    </string>

    <string name="bunad_paragraph">
        Bunad is a Norwegian umbrella term encompassing, in its broadest sense, a range
        of both traditional rural clothes as well as modern 20th-century folk costumes.
        The bunad movement has its root in 19th-century national romanticism, which
        included an interest for traditional folk costumes not only in Norway, but also
        in neighbouring countries such as Denmark and notably Germany. However, in Norway
        national romanticist ideas had a more lasting impact.
    </string>

    <string name="nightlife_paragraph">
        Oslos city center has a vibrant nightlife, and this is the area where most of the
        citys visitors chose to go out. It could be wise to navigate according to musical
        preferences: In and around the upper parts of Karl Johan street you can move to
        whatever is most popular at the moment, while you find a good selection of places
        with a more alternative/rock-oriented music profile around Youngstorget. Herr Nilsen
        and Buckleys Pub are good picks for those who like jazz and blues.
    </string>
</resources>